<resources xmlns:tools="http://schemas.android.com/tools">
    <string name="app_name">NITJ</string>
    <string name="l_bold" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_bold</string>
    <string name="l_black" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_black</string>
    <string name="l_black_italic" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_black_italic</string>
    <string name="l_bold_italic" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_bold_italic</string>
    <string name="l_italic" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_italic</string>
    <string name="l_light" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_light</string>
    <string name="l_light_italic" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_light_italic</string>
    <string name="l_regular" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/lato_regular</string>
    <string name="c_bold" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/corinthia_bold</string>
    <string name="c_regular" tools:ignore="ReferenceType">@font/corinthia_regular</string>
    <string name="start">Start</string>
    <string name="close">Close</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="no_department_data_found">No Department Data Found</string>
    <string name="departments">DEPARTMENTS</string>
    <string name="nit_jalandhar">NIT JALANDHAR</string>
    <string name="preference_file_name">my_data_file</string>
    <string name="nitj_about">Dr B R Ambedkar National Institute of Technology was established in the year 1987 as Regional Engineering College and was given the status of National Institute of Technology (Deemed University) by the Government of India on October 17, 2002 under the aegis of Ministry of Education (Shiksha Mantralaya), New Delhi. Now the Ministry of Education (Shiksha Mantralaya), Government of India has declared the Institute as “Institute of National Importance” under the act of Parliament-2007. A large number of reputed Industrial houses in the country visit the Institution and select the final year students as Engineers/ Management Trainees. As one of the National Institutes of Technology (NIT), the Institute has the responsibility of providing high quality education in Engineering, Technology and Sciences to produce competent technical and scientific manpower for the country. The Institute offers BTech, MTech, MSc, MBA and PhD programmes in the several disciplines of Engineering, Technology and Sciences.</string>
    <string name="mission_nitj"><![CDATA[To become a leading and unique institution of higher learning, offering state-of-the-art education, research and training in engineering and technology to students who are able and eager to become change agents for the industrial and economic progress of the nation. To nurture and sustain an academic ambience conducive to the development and growth of committed professionals for sustainable development of the nation and to accomplish its integration into the global economy. To strive to be a Swachch NIT providing a guarantee of clean hostel, clean mess, clean water and hygienic & wholesome food to its students]]></string>
    <string name="reaching_nitj">The city of Jalandhar is situated between the rivers Sutlej and Beas on National Highway 1. It is one of the important towns of Punjab and is known for rich educational, cultural and literary activities. It is an internationally renowned industrial centre for sports goods, leather goods and hand-tools. The city is 370 kms away from Delhi enroute to Amritsar and is easily accessible from Delhi by train or bus. The Shatabdi Express trains plying from New Delhi in the morning at 07.20 hrs and in the evening at16.30 hrs, are the best modes of travel to Jalandhar. This train takes less than 5 hours to reach Jalandhar City.\n\nThe institute is located on the G T Road bye pass at a distance of 15 kms from Jalandhar bus-stand, 12 kms from Jalandhar city railway station and 18 kms from Jalandhar Cantt railway station. It is at a walking distance of half a km from Bidhipur railway crossing. Auto rickshaw and taxi services are available regularly from railway stations as well as the bus-stand.</string>
</resources>